[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1972 Russian movie was the answer to Americas 2001:  A Space Odyssey. The Russian movie was later remade in 2002 with George Clooney.", "correct_answer": "Solaris", "incorrect_answers": ["Syriana", "Oceans 11", "Fail Safe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The mathematical constant e, one of the most important numbers in mathematics, is equal to which of these fractions?", "correct_answer": "none of these", "incorrect_answers": ["22/7", "278/10", "271828/10000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1987 he became the first football coach to have Gatorade splashed on his head.", "correct_answer": "Bill Parcells", "incorrect_answers": ["Barry Switzer", "Bill Cowher", "Bud Grant"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If you happen to be near a big cat (e.g. lion, tiger, lynx) that seems to be about to attack you, which of the following shouldn\u2019t you do in any case?", "correct_answer": "Turn back and run", "incorrect_answers": ["Scream and shout", "Try to look larger than you really are", "Stare at its eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What TV cat had the motto I hate meeces to pieces?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Jinks", "incorrect_answers": ["Miss Puss", "Sonja", "Katz"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the nutty saber-toothed male squirrel from Ice Age: Dawn of the Dinosaurs?", "correct_answer": "Scrat", "incorrect_answers": ["Sid", "Steve", "Scott"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Sigmoidoscopy is a medical examination of which internal organ?", "correct_answer": "Large intestine", "incorrect_answers": ["Gallbladder", "Brain cavity", "Uterus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 1000 people, how many acres of land would be in the village?", "correct_answer": "6000", "incorrect_answers": ["12000", "4000", "25000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the author of the novel East of Eden?", "correct_answer": "John Steinbeck", "incorrect_answers": ["Steven Spielberg", "Elia Kazan", "Eugene ONeill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tongue of a pangolin is so long that it is anchored to its pelvis.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the Latin phrase ceteris paribus mean?", "correct_answer": "All other things being equal", "incorrect_answers": ["Let the seller beware", "Let the buyer beware", "The case can not stand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tiananmen Square, which has been the site of a number of political events and student protests, is located in what Chinese city?", "correct_answer": "Beijing", "incorrect_answers": ["Shanghai", "Guangzhou", "Taipei"]}]